let harddivisionquestions = [
    {
        question: "What is 196 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "28",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 288 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "29",
        AnswerB: "31",
        AnswerC: "32",
        AnswerD: "33",
        correctAnswer: "32",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 296 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "36",
        AnswerB: "37",
        AnswerC: "38",
        AnswerD: "39",
        correctAnswer: "37",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 224 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "29",
        AnswerB: "31",
        AnswerC: "32",
        AnswerD: "33",
        correctAnswer: "32",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 160 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "30",
        AnswerB: "35",
        AnswerC: "40",
        AnswerD: "45",
        correctAnswer: "40",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 188 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "46",
        AnswerB: "47",
        AnswerC: "48",
        AnswerD: "49",
        correctAnswer: "47",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 234 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "38",
        AnswerB: "39",
        AnswerC: "40",
        AnswerD: "41",
        correctAnswer: "39",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 210 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "20",
        AnswerB: "25",
        AnswerC: "30",
        AnswerD: "35",
        correctAnswer: "30",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 144 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "18",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 228 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "37",
        AnswerB: "38",
        AnswerC: "39",
        AnswerD: "40",
        correctAnswer: "38",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 312 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "36",
        AnswerB: "37",
        AnswerC: "38",
        AnswerD: "39",
        correctAnswer: "39",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 324 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "34",
        AnswerB: "36",
        AnswerC: "37",
        AnswerD: "38",
        correctAnswer: "36",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 405 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "43",
        AnswerB: "45",
        AnswerC: "47",
        AnswerD: "49",
        correctAnswer: "45",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 322 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "45",
        AnswerB: "46",
        AnswerC: "47",
        AnswerD: "48",
        correctAnswer: "46",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 225 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "24",
        AnswerB: "25",
        AnswerC: "26",
        AnswerD: "27",
        correctAnswer: "25",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 336 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "46",
        AnswerB: "47",
        AnswerC: "48",
        AnswerD: "49",
        correctAnswer: "48",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 136 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "17",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 124 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "31",
        AnswerB: "32",
        AnswerC: "33",
        AnswerD: "34",
        correctAnswer: "31",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 352 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "42",
        AnswerB: "44",
        AnswerC: "46",
        AnswerD: "48",
        correctAnswer: "44",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 266 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "36",
        AnswerB: "37",
        AnswerC: "38",
        AnswerD: "39",
        correctAnswer: "38",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 276 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "42",
        AnswerB: "44",
        AnswerC: "46",
        AnswerD: "48",
        correctAnswer: "46",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 184 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "21",
        AnswerB: "22",
        AnswerC: "23",
        AnswerD: "24",
        correctAnswer: "23",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 222 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "26",
        AnswerB: "27",
        AnswerC: "28",
        AnswerD: "29",
        correctAnswer: "27",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 145 ÷ 5",
        AnswerA: "27",
        AnswerB: "28",
        AnswerC: "29",
        AnswerD: "31",
        correctAnswer: "29",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 152 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "37",
        AnswerB: "38",
        AnswerC: "39",
        AnswerD: "40",
        correctAnswer: "38",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 168 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "21",
        AnswerB: "22",
        AnswerC: "24",
        AnswerD: "26",
        correctAnswer: "24",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 304 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "32",
        AnswerB: "34",
        AnswerC: "36",
        AnswerD: "38",
        correctAnswer: "38",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 282 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "36",
        AnswerB: "37",
        AnswerC: "38",
        AnswerD: "39",
        correctAnswer: "37",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 315 ÷ 15",
        AnswerA: "21",
        AnswerB: "22",
        AnswerC: "23",
        AnswerD: "24",
        correctAnswer: "21",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 189 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "26",
        AnswerB: "27",
        AnswerC: "28",
        AnswerD: "29",
        correctAnswer: "27",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 279 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "31",
        AnswerB: "32",
        AnswerC: "33",
        AnswerD: "34",
        correctAnswer: "31",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 234 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "36",
        AnswerB: "37",
        AnswerC: "38",
        AnswerD: "39",
        correctAnswer: "39",
    },
]